本字幕由:Dex7er 使用
SubsPlayer制作，翻译:Gemini
"坦白说，我以前就是个被宠坏的、可悲的、自恋的、
自毁的、没头脑的毛头小子，而且极其欠揍。"
♪ Well, I'm going up,
up on Magic Mountain ♪
♪ 好了 我要登上 ♪ ♪ 《魔山》 ♪
♪ Well, I'm going so high,
we're gonna touch the sky ♪
♪ 好了 我要飞得好高
♪ ♪ 我们要去触摸天空 ♪
安东尼·波登 厨房机密档案
♪ Drink a little water,
up on Magic Mountain ♪
♪ 喝点水吧 ♪ ♪ 在《魔山》上 ♪
♪ Peace and love,
love, love, for you and I ♪
♪ 爱与和平 爱 爱 ♪ ♪ 属于你和我 ♪
瓦萨学院 1975年
Okay, so I'm just gonna walk you through
好吧 我来给你们
the basic vision of the story,
简单讲讲这个故事的构想
and you guys feel free to chime in
大家随时都可以
whenever you want, okay?
发表意见 好吗
So, what I'm trying to do
所以 我想做的是
is create a metaphorical conversation
在
between George Orwell and Jack Kerouac,
乔治·奥威尔和杰克·凯鲁亚克之间
as if Down and Out in Paris and London
展开一场隐喻性的对话
was typed out on one long piece of paper.
就好像《巴黎伦敦落魄
记》是用一张长纸打出来的
Snappy. Splenetic. High velocity.
干练 刻薄 节奏明快
At its core, it's a building's Roman,
它的核心
but not in the sad Salinger,
smoking, woman-hating way.
是一部成长小说 但不是那种悲伤的、
抽着烟的、厌女的塞林格风格
It's hopeful.
它是充满希望的
And I know I put it on my application,
我知道
but in terms of timeline,
我在申请表里写了 不过就时间线而言
I'd want to have the first draft done by July.
我希望在七月份前完成初稿
Then submit for notes
from this esteemed troika,
然后交给这三位尊敬的大佬审阅并提意见
do a quick polish,
快速润色一下
and hopefully spend the rest of my summer
然后希望我剩下的夏天
in a state of "boketto."
都能处于“发呆”的状态
That's what the Japanese say
日本人就是这么说的
when you gaze out in the distance
当你眺望远方
without thinking about anything in particular.
脑子里什么也不想的时候
All right. Very impressive, Anthony.
行了 非常令人印象深刻 安东尼
You know what?
Only my mother calls me Anthony.
你知道吗 只有我妈才叫我安东尼
Tony.
叫我托尼
Okay, then. Tony.
好吧 托尼
You'll be hearing from us soon.
我们很快就会联系你
And then they just sat there
and stared at me.
然后他们就坐在那儿盯着我看
- -I'm telling you,
-
these people are so fucking stupid it's insane.
-我跟你说 这些人蠢得要死 简直疯了
I said I was gonna write the whole thing
我说我要把整本书
on one piece of paper, and they believed me.
写在一张纸上 他们居然信了
They were... They were just nodding,
他们当时...
like I was explaining the rules of a brothel.
他们就只是点头
就像我在解释妓院的规矩一样
EI already found this Upper West Side place,
而且我已经在上西区找好地方了
right where Salinger grew up.
就在塞林格长大的地方附近
It's fucking perfect.
简直完美
Just gotta tell my parents
我只要告诉父母
that the fellowship takes place in New York,
这个写作津贴项目在纽约
and I'm outta here.
然后我就闪人了
Okay, but you gotta write a book?
好吧 但你得写本书啊
Yeah, but that's what I've
been trying to do all year.
对啊 但这正是我
一整年都在努力想做的事
I swear, it's like God is
finally starting to notice me.
我发誓 感觉上帝终于开始注意到我了
Word for that is "providence."
这叫“天意”
The word... The word for what?
这个词...什么词
It's when God fi...
就是上帝...
托尼
南希·普特科斯基
“对于有慧眼的人来说，
共时性是一个无时不在的现实。”
卡尔·荣格
♪ I was under the Calvary Cross ♪
♪ 我曾站在骷髅地十字架下 ♪
美国烹饪学院
招生办公室
So, it seems like...
所以 看起来...
your experience is washing dishes
你的经验就是
安东尼·波登于1975至2002年间在各大厨房工作
退休时任纽约莱斯哈雷斯餐厅行政主厨
♪ You don't have long to go ♪
♪ 你没剩多少时间了 ♪
♪ Remember me, remember me ♪
♪ 记住我 记住我 ♪
43岁时，他出版了《厨房机密档案：
餐饮业 N 面大公开》该书在全球已售出数百万册
♪ 'Cause I'm the one who made you see ♪
♪ 因为我是那个 让你看清真相的人 ♪
♪ Remember me ♪
♪ 记住我 ♪